[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Lorenzo Lamas appeared in the movie Grease, as the character who dated Sandy for a while.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following actors has not appeared in an adaptation of Akira Kurosawas film Yojimbo?", "correct_answer": "Kurt Russell", "incorrect_answers": ["Clint Eastwood", "Bruce Willis", "Christopher Walken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term means fear of fish?", "correct_answer": "Ichthyophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Iatrophobia", "Ideophobia", "Iophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Son of Godzilla (1967) the Big Guy has an offspring who looks nothing like him; in fact, his son is cute and cuddly.  What is the name of Godzillas son?", "correct_answer": "Minya", "incorrect_answers": ["Gyaos", "Jet Jaguar", "Sonzilla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By the end of what week does an unborn fetus start to develop fingerprints?", "correct_answer": "18th", "incorrect_answers": ["16th", "15th", "20th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following did Henry Ford not put into his first cars?", "correct_answer": "Reverse gear", "incorrect_answers": ["Steering wheel", "A place for a second person to sit in front", "Rear seats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Keep Their Heads Ringin is playing on the car radio when Smokey and Craig drive to the store in the film Friday.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the character voiced by Tom Hanks in the Toy Story movies?", "correct_answer": "Woody", "incorrect_answers": ["Slinky Dog", "Buzz Lightyear", "Rex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2005, this famous Russian cosmonaut set a record for total time, spent in space.", "correct_answer": "Sergei Krikalev", "incorrect_answers": ["Anatoly Solovyev", "Valeriy Polyakov", "Sergei Avdeyev"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These two additive primary colors should be combined in order to get the color yellow.", "correct_answer": "Green and red", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue and green", "White and red", "Red and blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 2003 horror movie Kyle Walsh must confront his troubled past and save his childhood sweetheart and her younger brother from an unrelenting evil.", "correct_answer": "Darkness Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["The Island of Dr. Moreau", "The House on the Edge of the Park", "The Funhouse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which villain do Han, Leia, C-3P0, Chewbacca, and R2-D2 meet in Cloud City?", "correct_answer": "Darth Vader", "incorrect_answers": ["Emperor Palpatine", "Darth Maul", "Darth Sidious"]}]